driverfinderpro.com 2015-05-08

# DriverFinder - Privacy Policy

* * *

This Privacy Policy describes the terms of our commitment to your privacy. 

### Persons or Parties Covered

This Privacy Policy covers the collection and use of personal information ("Personal Information") that we may gather any time you interact with us, such as when you visit our web site, try and/or use our product, or when you contact our customer support or sales departments. This Privacy Policy is intended to cover all visitors to this website, affiliates or business partners, and all customers. Persons who visit or view this website, whether intentionally or unintentionally, whether solicited or unsolicited, are described herein as "Visitors" and are parties to this Privacy Policy. People who join marketing endeavors (e.g. "affiliates") promoted by this website are called "Members" and are covered by this Privacy Policy. Anyone who orders, attempts to order, or receives a sold product advertised on or delivered from this website, even at no cost, is called a "Customer" and is subject to this Privacy Policy not only by passive acceptance, but by virtue of the Terms of Service contract. The website, its agents, owners, operators, and employees are referred to collectively herein as "Website" and/or "Site" and/or "We".

DeskToolsSoft Inc's DriverFinder has been certified by the TRUSTe's Trusted Download Program signifying that DriverFinder has been tested TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe's TDP program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding DriverFinder, please contact us at DeskToolsSoft, located at 548 Market Street, San Francisco, CA 94104 or by email at support@desktoolssoft.com or by phone at (408) 600-1418. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe **[here](http://clicktoverify.truste.com/pvr.php?page=validate&softwareProgramId=518&sealid=112)**.

### Persons Excluded From This Website Are Still Covered

Persons excluded from this website due to the Terms of Service or from denial of service by the website, who nonetheless unlawfully view this site remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and is in violation of the Terms of Service.

### Persons Under 18 Years Of Age Are Excluded From This Website

This website is not lawfully accessible to persons under the age of 18 or who are otherwise covered by the provisions of the Child Online Privacy Act of 1998 (COPA). If you are under the age of 18 you must leave this site immediately. Fraudulent use of this website may make you subject to civil or criminal sanctions.

### Viewing And/Or Use And/Or Communication Is Construed As Acceptance Of The Terms Of This Policy

Acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy is a portion of the consideration required for your right to visit the website. If you do not accept these terms, you have no right to visit this site and you are fraudulently using this site.

### A Note To California Residents (Online Privacy Protection Act Of 2003 - OPPA)

It is the intent of the Privacy Policy to comply with the California Act. Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the act. In summary, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. This is not usually personally identifiable. If you purchase a product or service via this website (and thereby become covered by the Act), the Terms of Service you electronically sign prior to purchase allows the website to collect and archive all the personal information you provide and to transmit and/or transfer that personal information to third parties. There is no way you can modify this information and you have no right to do so. Under the terms of the Terms of Service you have no right to view or receive any information about our database. In the event that the website, under advice of counsel agrees to divulge information, the requesting party must submit whatever information is demanded by the website in order to insure that the website is releasing information to the correct party. Other provisions of the OPPA may exempt this website from complying. While we take measures to ensure that outside parties do not have access to any information we have about you, we do not warranty that outside parties will not breach our system and thus have access to your information. (You should know that merchant service providers do not allow us access to your credit card information.)

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, our Home page, and other places we deem appropriate. We will also notify You via the Software when changes have been made to this Privacy Policy, and other documents such as our EULA, Terms of Service, etc. 

### Why We Collect Personal Information

This Website only collects your Personal Information, where it is required, to provide you the best services and products available. By maintaining an accurate customer database, we are able to send notifications via e-mail to keep you informed about the status of your orders or accounts and to provide updates and technical notices. These messages are essential to the maintenance of your subscription and the functionality of our products and services.

### About the Personal Information the DriverFinder Application Collects And How It Is Used

The driver scanning, matching and updating technology present in our software is designed to collect Hardware IDs and software signatures present in the system and routes this data back to our driver servers. We use this information so that our driver servers can respond back to our software with a list of recommended driver updates and other software relevant to the discovered hardware. While in trial-mode (pre-purchase, unregistered), this information is not tied in any way to any personal information. Post-purchase (registered) and after activation of the software the information is linked to your personal information. This information is also used to handle any technical, product, or customer support requests that you may send to us. Please be aware that if you prefer not to provide this inventory information, our software will be unable to provide any of our services. 

### About the Personal Information This Website Collects And How It Is Used

This website routinely collects information about its visitors, members, and customers. This information is obtained in various ways, such as:

### Visitor, Member, Or Customer Information Obtained From 'Registration'

Registration means that the Visitor, Member or Customer takes active, positive steps to communicate information to this website. This can include pages where you register for Customer Support; it can include requesting information from the website via email, mail, or courier; it may be from joining an affiliate program or other membership organization, paid or unpaid; it may be from ordering a product.

For Customer Support registration instances, data is collected by:  
DeskToolsSoft at the [DeskToolsSoft/DriverFinder Customer Support Portal](http://desktoolssoft.com/support/).  
548 Market Street  
San Francisco, CA 94104  
E-mail: info[at]desktoolssoft[dot]com 

For Product Registration instances, data is collected by:  
1205 - 4464 Markham Street Victoria, BC V8Z 7X8  
E-mail: customersupport[at]safecart[dot]com 

For general inquiries, data is collected by:  
DriverFinder at the [DriverFinder Contact Us form](http://driverfinderpro.com/contact.php).  
548 Market Street  
San Francisco, CA 94104  
E-mail: info[at]driverfinderpro[dot]com 

### Commitment to Data Security

This Website DOES NOT store credit card information. We work with a select number of 3rd party payment processors who serve as a trusted intermediary to handle e-commerce transactions with our Customers. Our e-commerce partners handle e-commerce on secure servers which encrypt all of our Customers' personal information. To learn more about how our e-commerce partners manage the privacy of information in conjunction with these e-commerce transactions, please see their complete Privacy Statements located on their purchase pages.

This Website has security measures in place, such as the following, to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your Personal Information in our customer database. Personal Information provided is stored in secure facilities with access restricted to authorized personnel only. We also have in place a series of access-control procedures required for retrieval of personal information. Further, this Website is regularly tested for security breaches to protect against unauthorized viewing of Personal Information. Although we make substantial efforts to store any Personal Information we collect in a secure operating environment that is not accessible to unauthorized users, no one - including this Website - can guarantee complete security.

### Visitor Email Inquiries

Visitors who wish to communicate with the Website do so under two conditions: one, they give their permission for contact by the website; two, they are subject to any 'submission' provisions of the Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy. While your email address may or may not be used to solicit you, it is added to the website's general solicitation database.

### Customer Email Or Testimonials

If you are a customer and send an email to the website, or if you communicate with the site by phone or mail, the website collects information about your communication and by communicating with the site you give your permission to collect, archive, retrieve, and otherwise use any information collected as the site sees fit.

However, we will not, under any circumstances, share, merge, rent or sell your Personal Information in ways other than as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We also do not trade or exchange mailing lists with any other organization.

Any communication which, in its sole discretion, the site deems to be a testimonial, may be publicized for commercial purposes.

### Information Obtained From Referring Email Or Referring Urls

If you send a friend an email about this Site or if you send our url or that of one of our web pages to a friend, you must assume that some data is collected about your IP address or your email address and that of your friend. You must accept full responsibility for referring pages or email to a friend and agree to indemnify this site for any damage, intentional or unintentional, that results from said referrals.

### Information Obtained From Voluntary Visitor, Member Or Customer Surveys

Unless otherwise specified in the survey, you must assume that any information provided to the website as part of a survey in which you participate may be used for general solicitation for commercial purposes or used by the site itself for product design or solicitation purposes.

However, we will not, under any circumstances, share, merge, rent or sell your Personal Information in ways other than as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We also do not trade or exchange mailing lists with any other organization.

### Information Obtained From Electronic Means And 'Cookies'

Many websites, including this one, collect information about your computer, your email address, your IP address. You must assume that your web-viewing or web-use activity is monitored, tracked, and information collected. This information is not usually of a personal nature, but it may help define your viewing habits and product preferences even though the website may or may not have any idea who you are.

"Cookies" is web jargon for bits of computer code placed on your hard drive. Websites use this to keep you 'logged in', to keep track of search criteria, to monitor use, to password protect use of the site or use of products sold by the site. Cookies can also be used to obtain information about your computer configuration or your use of your computer.

Cookies can be used to electronically gather information about you. Again, it may or may not be personal information, but it is information and by using this site you are expressly giving permission to use 'cookies' and to use the information gathered from their use to benefit you. You also give permission to collect, archive, retrieve, and use any information collected for product design, product offers to you, and general commercial solicitation purposes by this site or joint venture partners, affiliates, and marketing organizations.

### Opt-Out Information

DriverFinder provides a number of ways for you to OPT OUT of receiving additional information from us. Note that this option does not apply to communication sent for the purposes of administering orders, contracts, support, product safety warnings, software updates, or other administrative and transactional notices. If you do not wish to continue receiving additional information or certain marketing materials (e.g., e-mail messages), you can opt-out of receiving these materials by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the materials. 

In addition, you can correct out-of-date information, update information, remove information, delete your Personal Information or review any information previously provided to us by accessing your account at our [Customer Support portal](http://www.desktoolssoft.com/support/) or by contacting our Customer Support department at support[at]driverfinderpro[dot]com. Changes will be implemented within 10 business days. Please note, however, that we may retain certain information relating to software licensing and your information may also be retained in our archives. When contacting Customer Support, we may verify your identification through the use of security questions before sharing any Personal Information as it appears in our customer database.

### Sharing Your Personal Information

This Website is committed to protecting your privacy. We will not, under any circumstances, share, rent or sell your Personal Information in ways other than as outlined in this Privacy Policy nor does this Website trade or exchange mailing lists with any other organization. This Website only shares your Personal Information with our contractors that assist us in our efforts to fulfill our obligations to you, and then only with partners that commit to adhere to the same level of commitment as We do to protect your privacy and data. We use 3rd party payment processing companies to invoice you for goods and services and these companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

The 3rd party payment processing company we use is:  
1205 - 4464 Markham Street Victoria, BC V8Z 7X8  
E-mail: customersupport[at]safecart[dot]com 

### Bulletin Boards And Public Forums

Visitors, Members, or Customers who use any site provided bulletin boards or other public forums, such as chat rooms, do so at their own risk. You may not assume that the site monitors these services or protects you in any manner from information you post publicly or share with anyone else via these services.

### E-Mail

By providing to this website information that forms the basis of communication with you, such as an email address, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited email or spam from this website since, by providing such information, you agree to receive communication from us. However, all email communication with you shall contain an 'unsubscribe' link where you may notify the website that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information from the website and your name will be removed from the general solicitation database.

### Questions, Comments, or Report of Incidents

You may direct questions, comments or reports to: info [at] driverfinderpro [dot] com.

### Revisions To This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, our Home page, and other places we deem appropriate. We will also notify You via the Software when changes have been made to this Privacy Policy, and other documents such as our EULA, Terms of Service, etc. 

### Latest Update

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: May 9, 2014.

### Disputes

As part of the consideration that the Website requires of the Visitor to view, use, or interact with this site, Visitor agrees to use binding arbitration for any claim, dispute, or controversy ("CLAIM") of any kind (whether in contract, tort or otherwise) arising out of or relating to this purchase, this product, including solicitation issues, privacy issues, and Terms of Service issues.

Arbitration shall be conducted pursuant to the rules of the American Arbitration Association, which are in effect on the date a dispute is submitted to the American Arbitration Association. Information about the American Arbitration Association, its rules, and its forms are available from the American Arbitration Association, 335 Madison Avenue, Floor 10, New York, New York, 10017-4605. Hearing will take place in the city or county of the Seller.

In no case shall the Visitor have the right to go to court or have a jury trial. Visitor will not have the right to engage in pre-trial discovery except as provided in the rules; you will not have the right to participate as a representative or member of any class of claimants pertaining to any claim subject to arbitration; the arbitrator's decision will final and binding with limited rights of appeal.

The prevailing party shall be reimbursed by the other party for any and all costs associated with the dispute arbitration, including attorney fees, collection fees, investigation fees, travel expenses.

### Jurisdiction And Venue

If any matter concerning this purchase shall be brought before a court of law, pre- or post-arbitration, Visitor agrees to that the sole and proper jurisdiction to be the state and city declared in the contact information of the web owner unless otherwise here specified. 548 Market St., San Francisco, CA 94104. In the event that litigation is in a federal court, the proper court shall be the closest federal court to the Seller's address.

### Applicable Law

Visitor agrees that the applicable law to be applied shall, in all cases, be that of the state of the Website owner(s).
